#### Contact

antymijaljevic@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/antemijaljevic-839a29163 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Networking

Linux

Troubleshooting

#### Certifications

Python Essential Training
Certified Linux Administrator
(LPIC-1)
CompTIA Linux+
CompTIA Network +
CompTIA A+

Honors-Awards
Non-Article 5 NATO Medal

# Ante Mijaljevic

IT Technician Astreya Partners on behalf of Google

## Summary

Experienced and knowledgeable information technology professional. Terrific troubleshooting and good interpersonal skills to assist customers with computer issues. Possesses a thorough knowledge of computer hardware and software applications. Comfortable working with Unix based operating systems like Debian/Red Hat Linux, macOS, and scripting in Bash and Python. Solid with front end HTML&CSS. Have an understanding of TCP/IP and networking concepts.

## Experience

Astreya on behalf Google
IT Technician
June 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Dublin, Ireland

Inventory and asset management, conference room preventative maintenance, and e-recycling

Supporting a complex and fast paced environment focused on video conference rooms with outstanding attention to customer satisfaction. Ensuring audio and visual quality, troubleshooting any issues that may arise and any requests from meeting attendees. Laptop and desktop imaging, deployment and recovery. Customer support for over 70,000 users worldwide from IT accessory to workstation dressing.

Using ticketing systems to report individual work accomplishments and to track Service Level Agreements (SLAs).

Utilizing Inventory Data management software to maintain inventory accuracy and workflow

Contributing to large scale global projects as needed

Threadstone Security
Customer Service and Security Officer
2016 - 2018 (2 years)

Dublin, Ireland

Securing premises and personnel by patrolling property; monitoring surveillance equipment; inspecting buildings, equipment, and access points; permitting entry. Customer service. Completing reports by recording observations, Information, occurrences, and surveillance activities: interviewing witnesses; obtaining signatures. Preventing losses and damage by reporting irregularities.

Ministry of Defence of the Republic of Croatia Army Infantry Regiment, Specialist 2013 - 2015 (2 years)

Gospic, Croatia, Bishkek, Kyrgyzstan

#### **NATO**

Army Infantry Regiment, Specialist 2012 - 2013 (1 year) Mazar-e-Sharif, Afghanistan

Ministry of Defence of the Republic of Croatia Army Infantry Regiment 2009 - 2012 (3 years) Gospic, Croatia

PC Servis d.o.o IT Desktop support lvl1/lvl2 2007 - 2009 (2 years) Zadar, Croatia

- Ensured the seamless functionality of office equipment, such as video conferencing hardware, printers, desk phones, and computers. This was done by answering support tickets with resourcefulness along with prioritizing and logical thinking.
- PXE boot deployment of Linux, Mac Os and Windows desktop and laptop machines.
- Worked alongside TechStop (IT Support) teams to provide hardware solutions and fix's for any issues the tech's would encounter.

## Education

New Horizons Computer Learning Center - Dublin

CompTIA CIOS, CSSS, CLNP, Information Technology · (2017 - 2019)